Let's get this journey underway.
First thing we want to do is download Python.
That's pretty simple.
All you've got to do is go to Python.org downloads, and you will be prompted to download the latest
version for your operating system.
You can see we're using a mac, so it's going to download the Mac version, but it should default to
whatever operating system you're using.
If it doesn't, you can obviously just click on the link and download the appropriate version for your
operating system.
Just download the latest version three.
It doesn't matter what version it is or subversion of version three, you're going to be basing everything
on Python three, so download whichever one is currently the latest when you're doing the course, and
that should work just perfectly.
So quite simple.
Simply click on the link and save it, and we'll show you how to install it and we'll be ready to go.